letuofly.com 2019-01-27

# Privacy Notice : letuofly.com, Your online shopping store

Maintaining the privacy of your information is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, and store personal information that users (“you” or “User”) provide to us through websites and/or mobile applications (collectively, “online sites”) operated by us. 

By using our online sites and/or submitting your personal information to us, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our online sites and/or provide us with your personal information. 

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. If any such changes impact the way we collect or use your personal information, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted. We encourage you to regularly review this Privacy Policy to make sure you are aware of any changes and how your information may be used.  If at any point we decide to use your personal information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify Users by email or via a prominent notice on our website and where necessary, we will seek the prior consent of our Users.

**Collection of Personal Information**

To simply browse our online sites, we do not ask you to provide any information. However, if you wish to participate in any of the features and services our online sites have to offer, we may ask you to provide certain personal and/or demographic information such as your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, credit card information (“personally identifiable information”) and/or your date of birth, age, gender, habits and preferences, usernames, and passwords when such information is tied with your personally identifiable information (collectively, “personal information”). Personal information is only collected with your consent (i.e., if you knowingly provide it to us) and usually take the form of (1) online registration or sign-up; (2) surveys or polls; (3) product purchase transactions; (4) feedback, questions or comments through our “Contact Us” form and; (5) any other request that requires the submission of personal information. 

**Security of Personal Information**

We adopts all necessary and appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, use, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction and credit card information, and data stored on our online sites.

**Use of Personal Information**

Generally, all information collected is used for the purpose for which you submitted the information to us or as otherwise identified at the point of collection or in this Privacy Policy. For example, if you sign up for a product warranty registration or purchase a product on our online sites, the information you provide is used to offer you the notices, benefits and privileges that typically come along with the specific registration or transaction. Similarly, if you contact us via an online contact form, your information is used to process and respond to your inquiry or comment.

When registering or providing information on our online sites, you may also be given the option (through a check box or otherwise) to have your information used for an activity or service different from the primary activity or service that you are requesting. For example, if you are registering for a product warranty or purchasing a product, you may also be able to sign up for newsletters, alerts, or promotions from other third party websites or our products.

We may also use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies so we can constantly improve, personalize, and customize the products and services we provide you and to better meet your needs. This may include occasionally combining, updating, or otherwise enhancing the personal information collected through our online sites with data we receive from outside records or third parties.

Generally, we retain your personal information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you the services requested. If you request that we no longer use your personal information to provide you services (e.g., opt-out of receiving email), please call us or email us, that your personal information will be retained for a reasonable period of time and as necessary to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, and similar records management purposes.
